Right
大家好
My name is Fons
我叫Fons
And in this video I will show you how to install Julia
在本视频中，我将向您展示如何安装Julia
the programming language
Julia是一门编程语言
and Pluto, the programming environment
以及Pluto，这是Julia的编程环境
there's also a written version of this video available
该视频有一个书面版本
and there is also description
还有说明
And if you have any questions
如果有任何疑问
you can email us
你可以给我们发电子邮件
so the first thing we do is to install Julia
所以我们要做的第一件事是安装Julia
so we go to JuliaLang.org
打开JuliaLang.org
and here it allows us to install
在这里我们可以安装下载Julia 1.5.1
which is the current stable release
这是当前的稳定版本
and so you find the platform that you have
您可以找到您自己的平台
in my case it's Windows
我的电脑是Windows
You need click on the little help next to your OS
而你需要单击操作系统旁边的Help
so we click
所以我们单击
I already read this before
我已经读过了
but it just tells us to download the installer, run it
它主要是告诉我们下载安装程序，运行它
and we can also add it to our path
我们也可以将Julia添加到系统路径中
You don't really need it for our course
但在课程里面暂时不需要它
but maybe you want it added later
你也许之后会希望再添加
You can read this on your own if you like
如果愿意，你可以自己阅读这些文档
So let's go to these downloads
因此，让我们直接看下载部分
and in my case I need the 64-bit installer
我自己而言，需要64位安装程序
I save it
然后保存
and while it is downloading
并且在正在下载的时候
maybe you can have a look around this website
也许你可以浏览这个网站
It has a bunch of resources to learn Julia
网站里拥有大量资源，可以很好地学习Julia
all right so downloaded and let's run
好了，下载完了，然后运行这个安装
so take a minute to do install ... OK
所以安装可能需要一点时间...好了
I'm just going to click next, etc.
我准备一直“下一步”安装
And I'll pause, and see you when it's done
好的，我会暂停录制，然后等好了再开始录制
Okey, it's done and let's click finish
OK，完成了，让我们单击完成
And now whenever we want to start Julia
现在，每当我们要启动Julia时
You just go to the start menu
您只需转到开始菜单
and then it will be here, Julia 1.5.1
然后可以在这里运行Julia 1.5.1
so now we end up in something called REPL (Read-Evaluate-Print-Loop)
所以现在我们来到了称为REPL的交互式编程环境
and this is where it can accept commands
这是我们可以输入指令
you should try out
可以尝试输入
can you do 1 plus 1, ..., 2, he works
1+1，回车，结果2，说明Julia安装成功了
So here you type your Julia commands
所以Julia命令都是在这里输入
but to install Pluto,
但是要安装Pluto，
Pluto is a Julia package because Pluto is written in Julia
Pluto是Julia软件包，因为Pluto是用Julia编写的
now we need to open a package manager
现在我们需要打开一个包管理器
and in Julia the package manager is built into the REPL
在Julia中，软件包管理器内置在REPL中
So what you do is
因此，为了要进入这包管理器
you press that closing bracket ...
按下右方括号
closing square bracket sign, ..., this sign
按下右方括号，这里输入了井号是为了演示该输入哪个符号
and if you type that into the REPL without the hash at the start
并且在REPL中不输入井号就按下右方括号
you end up in the package manager
就可以进入了包管理器
and this is where I can type package commands instead of Julia commands
这是只能键入包命令，而不能输入Julia语句
So this one doesn't work here it needs package commands
所以输入1+1在这里不起作用，它需要打包命令
and the package commands we will give it was `add Pluto`
而我们将给它的打包命令是“add Pluto“
and if you run it
如果你运行它
it'll take a minute because we're doing this for the first time
这将需要一分钟，因为这是是第一次这样做
and it's setting up the package environments on the registry et cetera
它正在注册表等上设置软件包环境
so I'll pause again and I'll see you when it's done
所以我会再次暂停录制本视频，等完成后开始
So it's done
现在完成了
and now I'm going to press Backspace and back into the Julia REPL
现在我要按Backspace键并回到Julia REPL中
Back into Julia REPL I will type 'import Pluto'
回到Julia REPL，我将输入“import Pluto”
press enter
按Enter
then it says
然后屏幕显示
to start a notebook server you do `Pluto.run()`
要启动笔记本服务器，请执行`Pluto.run()`。
let's give it a minute to load
启动笔记本需要花一点时间加载
Pluto.run()
输入“Pluto.run()”
and now it's telling us to go to localhost:1234 in your browser
现在它告诉我们，在浏览器中访问localhost:1234
so if you press Ctrl+C in the terminal
如果您在终端中按Ctrl + C
that's how you stop Pluto
这是用来停止Pluto的
so don't copy this using Ctrl+C
所以不要试图使用Ctrl + C复制
it's different in the terminal for some reason
由于某些原因，终端里面不能够用这种方式复制
OK so in the browser (you need Firefox or Chrome btw)
确定，因此在浏览器中（浏览器需要Firefox或Chrome）
you go to localhost:1234
输入localhost:1234
You see I have typed it already
你可以看到我之前已经访问过这个网站了
And you go there, it's loading and says welcome to Pluto
然后显示正在加载，欢迎来到Pluto
and so if you've seen this for the first time
如果你是第一次看到这个
which you probably are
（很可能你的确是第一次看到这个）
then you might want to have a look at these sample notebooks
那么最好看看这些示例笔记本
Take click here
点击这里
and these are meant to introduce you to Pluto
这些笔记本旨在向您介绍Pluto
but also a bit to mathematics and to Julia code
并且如果你是Julia的新手
if you're new to Julia
这些笔记本也可以对数学和Julia代码有所了解
I recommend having looked at 1,2 and 6
我建议看看笔记本1,2和6
Because they explain... they also teach you a bit of Julia
因为他们是Julia很好的入门
Right, so in our case
好的，在这个视频中
we want to work on homework 0
我们的目标是完成课后作业0
so we go to the github for the course page
所以我们去github查看课程页面
and then we go to homework 0
然后我们去做homework0
and so this, the hw0.jl
这个hw0.jl文件
is the link to the notebook file
这是我们作业的notebook文件的链接
So you take this link, copy
点击此链接，复制
and then here you Paste
然后在此处粘贴
press open
按打开
are you sure and you say Yes, I'm sure
“你确定吗？”，选择“是的，我确定”
and what it will do in this homework 0 is based on a template notebook
本作业将会在以这个笔记本作为模板
and you have to start out from the template notebook
你需要从模板笔记本开始
adding your own stuff and then sending a book back to us
添加一些你自己的代码，然后再上传给我们
and so right now
所以现在
it's starting Pluto for the first time
让我们第一次启动Pluto
which is why it takes a while
这就是为什么启动需要一段时间
And it just downloaded the notebook
这是因为它在下载
the template notebook
我们用到的模板笔记本
and it's running it
它正在运行
so the first thing one to do before anything else
因此首先要做的第一件事
is to save this notebook
是要保存此笔记本
So right now it isn't saved anywhere
所以现在它没有保存在任何地方
so let's first create a folder
所以我们首先创建一个文件夹
And this is different on every OS
这在每个操作系统上都不同
but I'm on windows so
但我在Windows上
go to file explorer
所以我们打开文件资源管理器
let's say Documents
比如说“我的文档”
New folder, 18S191 SUBMISSIONS
建立文件夹，输入自己的名字
what we need now is the path to this folder
由于我们需要获得这个文件夹的路径
so go inside the folder which is empty
所以进入这个文件夹，文件夹还是空的
and then I do right click, Properties
然后右键单击“属性”
and this tells me where this folder is exactly
可以获得文件夹的确切位置
So this is where you want to save this notebook
假设这就是你保存作业0笔记本的地方
So you go here
所以点到这里
And this is where you type the file
可以输入路径名字
so I paste, this
然后粘贴
and then it was 18...SUBMISSIONS...(Using tab to auto-complete)
然后输入18... SUBMISSIONS...（使用Tab自动补全）
that's called this homework 0
好的，然后把笔记本命名为homework 0...
my name is Fonsi
...fonsi，这是我的名字
Here you go
好的
and so next you just work on a notebook
接下来，你只需在笔记本里面写代码
The instructions are inside the notebook
作业的说明和提示都在笔记本里面
when you're done
完成后
this is where the file is
这是文件所在的位置
and you can see it in the folder
可以在文件夹中看到这个新的笔记本
and so to submit it to canvas
并提交给MIT的作业叫系统Canvas
you go to canvas
在Canvas里面
and then there's an assignment
可以看到然后有一个作业
called homework 0
叫做作业0
you click, and then here to submit the file
点击，然后在此处提交文件
the file upload is this Julia file
需要上传的就是这个Julia文件
there you go
好的，就到这里
have fun
祝你玩得开心
and let's see you soon
我们下期再见